Guide to the Paul LeBlanc Papers, 1967-1998 AIS.1974.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications, I.
  - Socialist Challenge (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
  - Socialist Democracy (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Socialist Forum (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
  - Socialist Organiser (Box 10, Item 2)
  - Socialist Outlook (Box 10, Folder 8-12)
  - Socialist Review (Box 10, Item 3-6)
  - "Socialist Scholars Conference" Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Tribune (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Worker (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Socialist Workers Party Discussion Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 16-25)
  - Socialist Workers Party Information Bulletin (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Socialist Workers Party Internal Information Bulletin (Box 11, Folder 4-8)
  - Socialist Workers Party Organizational Discussion Bulletin (Box 11, Folder 9-10)
  - Socialist Workers Party - Party Organizer (Box 11, Folder 11-12)
  - Sojourners (Box 11, Item 1)
  - Solidarity Discussion Bulletin (Box 11, Folder 13-25)
  - Solidarity Discussion Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
  - Solidarity Discussion Papers (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Solidarity Student and Youth Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Solidarity Youth and Student Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - South End Press Catalog (Box 12, Item 1)
  - Southpaw Books (Box 12, Item 2)
  - Spartacist (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Spring Movement (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - The Stark Fist of Removal (Box 12, Item 3)
  - Starving Amidst too Much by T-Bone Slim (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Steel Valley Authority: A Community Plan to Save Pittsburgh's Steel Industry (Box 12, Item 4)
  - Steelabor (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Steelworker's Voice (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Straight Track (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Strike Back: A Weekly Bulletin for Workers and the Unemployed (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Student Activism in the 1980's (Box 12, Item 5)
  - Student Peace Union Discussion Bulletin (Box 12, Item 6-9)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Synthesis/Regeneration 17 (Box 12, Item 10-11)
  - TDU: 10 Years and Going Strong (Box 12, Item 12)
  - Teamster Convoy Dispatch (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Telos (Box 12, Item 13)
  - Third World Viewpoint (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Towards a Mass and Democratic Student Peace Union Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - The Transitional Program: Forging a Revolutionary Agenda for the U.S. (Box 12, Item 14)
  - Tikkun (Box 12, Item 15)
  - Transforming Congregations for the Future by Loren B. Mead (Box 12, Item 16)
  - Tri-State Conference Call (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Trotskyist International (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Tucson First Annual Each-I (Box 12, Item 17)
  - Turning Problems into Opportunities by Wendi Taylor (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - UE News (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Union Democracy Review (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Unions and Free Trade (A Labor Notes Book) (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Unity and Struggle (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - The University Times (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - U.S. News and World Report (Box 12, Item 18-20)
  - USLA Reporter (Box 12, Item 21)
  - Vanguard Newsletter (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - The VDC News (Box 12, Item 22)
  - Viet Report (Box 12, Item 23-26)
  - The View from Here (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Views (Box 12, Item 27)
  - The Village Voice (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Voice Literary Supplement (Box 12, Item 28)
  - The Volunteer (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - The Washington Spectator (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Welcome! Tools and Techniques for New Member Ministry by Andrew D. Weeks (Box 12, Item 29)
  - West Coast Sailors (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - When Democracy is on the Job, America Works (Box 12, Item 30)
  - Which Way America? (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Wildcat (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Wildcat Report (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Why Socialism? (Box 12, Item 31)
  - Witness for Peace (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Women and Revolution (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - The Worker (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Worker Today (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Workers and Trade Union Movement Information Centre (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Workers as Owners Published by the Labor Research Review (Box 12, Item 32)
  - Workers League Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Workers' Liberty (Box 12, Item 33-36)
  - Worker's Power (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Workers Power Discussion Bulletin (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Workers Press (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Workers Review (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Workers Struggle (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Workers Vanguard (Box 13, Folder 6-8)
  - Workers Voice (Box 13, Item 1)
  - Workers World (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Working People (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Working Stiff Journal (Box 13, Item 2)
  - The Working Teamster (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Working Together, Labor Report on the Americas (Box 13, Item 3)
  - A Year of Decision for U.S. Labor: The Hormel Strike and Beyond (Box 13, Item 4)
  - Young Communist (Box 13, Item 5)
  - The Young Socialist (Box 13, Item 6)
  - Young Socialist Alliance (YSA) Discussion Bulletin (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
  - Young Socialist Forum (Box 13, Item 7)
  - Young Worker's Liberation League (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Z Magazine (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
- Fourth Internationalist Tendency (F.I.T.), II.
  The material in this series pertains to the publications, organization, and functioning of the F.I.T. Included in this series are the F.I.T. publications Bulletin in Defense of Marxism, Internal Information Bulletin and Internal Discussion Bulletin, among others. There are also many reports, memos, meeting minutes and correspondences that show how the F.I.T. was organized and functioned. In addition, there is material concerning the F.I.T. and its relationships with other similar organizations.
  - F.I.T. Flyers (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - F.I.T. Pamphlets and Newsletters (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - F.I.T. Pamphlets (Box 13, Folder 19-20)
  - F.I.T. Publications (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - F.I.T. Publishing Related Material (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - F.I.T. Materials for a History of Trotskyism in the U.S. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - F.I.T. Information Letter, 1985-1992 (Box 13, Folder 25-40)
  - F.I.T. Educational Bulletin (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism (Box 14, Item 1-35)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Related Material (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Name and Subject Index, December 1983-December 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Functioning (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Editorial Board Mailings and Committee Minutes (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Finances (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Style Sheet (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Arsenals (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Reviews (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - F.I.T. Editorial Commission and Bulletin in Defense of Marxism Related Material (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - F.I.T. and the Bulletin in Defense of Marxism (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - F.I.T. Internal Discussion Bulletin, 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 14-31)
  - F.I.T. Internal Information Bulletin, 1988-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1-11)
  - F.I.T. Internal Bulletins (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - F.I.T. Information Bulletin - The September 1988 Plenum of the National Organizing Committee, November 1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - F.I.T. Discussion Bulletins and Pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correction to an F.I.T. Information Bulletin (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Articles on F.I.T. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - F.I.T. Business Correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - F.I.T. Personal Correspondence, 1985-1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - F.I.T. Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
  - Correspondence between Joanna Misnik, Steve Bloom and Paul LeBlanc, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Steve Bloom Correspondence and Articles, 1990-1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Steve Bloom Correspondence and Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Alan Wald Correspondence and Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - F.I.T. Artwork (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - F.I.T. (Box 15, Folder 26-33)
  - F.I.T. Reports, 1957-1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - F.I.T. Staff, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - F.I.T. Proposals, Resolutions and Discussions, 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - F.I.T. Proposals, 1985-1993 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - F.I.T. Documents and Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - F.I.T. Memos, Proposals and Resolutions, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - F.I.T. National and Local Organizing Committee Reports and Proposals (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1982 & 1990 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - F.I.T. National Coordinators Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - F.I.T. National Organizing Committee (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - F.I.T. Political Committee Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - F.I.T. Political Committee (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Local Organizing Committee of Cincinnati Minutes and Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local Organizing Committee of Cleveland Minutes and Agendas, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local Organizing Committee of Pittsburgh Minutes and Agendas, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local Organizing Committee Notes and Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local Organizing Committees Minutes, Reports and Memos, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Fourth International Caucus, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Fourth International Caucus, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Fourth International Caucus (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Fourth International Caucus Committee Business, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Fourth International Caucus Fund Commission, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Fourth International Caucus Mailings (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Discussion Bulletin of the F.I. Caucus of Solidarity, August 1994 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - F.I.T. Educational Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Paul LeBlanc's 1989 F.I.T. Conference Material (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Paul LeBlanc's 1992 F.I.T. Conference Material (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - F.I.T. Plenums and Conferences, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - F.I.T. Plenum, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Education Report for F.I.T. May 1991 Plenum (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Registration Forms for the 1992 National Conference (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - F.I.T.'s Anti-Intervention Commission (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - Anti-Intervention Publicity, Newsletters and Pamphlets, 1988-1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Anti-Intervention Commission Notes, Reports and Memos, 1983-1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - F.I.T.'s Cuba Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - F.I.T.'s Women's Liberation Commission, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - F.I.T. in Germany, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - F.I.T., Socialist Action and Socialist Workers Party Interactions, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Relations Between Socialist Actions, Socialist Workers Party, F.I.T. and Solidarity, 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Unity Process (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - F.I.T. Unity Subcommittee, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - F.I.T. Information-Gathering About Solidarity, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - F.I.T. Unity with Solidarity, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - F.I.T. and Socialist Action Unity and Relations, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Articles on Socialist Action and F.I.T. Unity, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - I.E.C., 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - I.E.C. and United Secretariat (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - United Secretariat Bureau, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - United Secretariat (Box 16, Folder 40-41)
  - F.I.T. Correspondence with United Secretariat, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Report on the October 5-11, 1991 United Secretariat Meeting (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - "Building the FI Today", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - "Pragmatic Manifesto of the FI", 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - F.I.T. 50th Anniversary, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - F.I.T. Book, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - FIC Book Membership, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Fourth International 50 Years New York Celebration - Member Biographies and Messages, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Ernest Mandel Tour, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Lawsuit with Pathfinder Press, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - F.I.T. Memo Paper (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Organizations, III.
  This series contains material related to the various organizations of which LeBlanc was interested or a member. The scope of the organizations varies from political, social, environmental, and charitable activities. Included are memos, letters, and meeting minutes, as well as flyers, pamphlets and bulletins. The most notable organizations are Solidarity, Socialist Workers Party and Socialist Action – groups that the F.I.T. dealt with closely.
  - Activists for Independent Socialist Politics (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - African-American Work Commission Report (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Allegheny Socialists (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Alliance for Progressive Action (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - American Labor Today Movement, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - American Trotskyism Project, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Autumn National Action, July 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore Press and Freedom Movement, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Black Action Society (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Black Construction Coalition (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Black Panther Party (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Black Workers for Justice (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Branch Meetings - Notes (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Campaign for a New Tomorrow (Box 17, Item 1)
  - Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Carnegie-Mellon University (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Center for Studies of Social Change (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition (Box 17, Folder 18-23)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Articles (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Pledge Mailing List, May 1984 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition and Labor (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Letters (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Landau Film (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Mailing List, May & July 1984 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition Proposals (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Central America Mobilization Coalition and CISPES (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Cleveland Area National Peace Action Coalition (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Coalition for Human Needs (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Committees of Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 34-36)
  - Committees of Correspondence - Western Pennsylvania Branch Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Common Cause (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Carry it On Peace Calendar 1999 (Box 17, Item 2)
  - Communist Party, USA (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party 25th National Convention, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2-5)
  - Congress of Racial Equality - Berkeley Campus (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Crisis in Black-Jewish Relations, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Daniels Campaign (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Drug, Hospital and Healthcare Employees Union (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - DSA Feminist Commission, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Defense Campaign, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Emergency National Council Against U.S. Intervention in Central America and the Caribbean (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - ECCA (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Faction for the Trotskyist International, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
  - Fifth of June Society (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Frank Lovell Memorial (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Freedom Socialist Party, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Freedom Socialist Party, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - **G Conference Pre-Conference Discussion Bulletin, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Gene Pepi Defense Committee (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Giant Eagle (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Historians of American Communism, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Humanity Books (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - IFCO Letter, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Industrial Director's Report (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - I.I.R.E., 1987 (Box 18, Folder 29-36)
  - International Socialists (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - JOIN Community Union, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Kansas City Socialists (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Knights of Labor (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Kroger Strike (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Labor Notes Conference Material and Notes, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Labor Party (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
  - Labor Party Conference (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "Living Wage Campaign" (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Mark Curtis Defense Committee, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Forum and Community of Reconciliation (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Michel Warschawsky and the Alternative Information Center Defence Campaign, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Midwest Radical Scholars and Activists Conference, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Militant Action Caucus (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - NCIPA (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - National Peace Action Coalition (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - National Committee to Combat Fascism (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - National Coordinating Committee (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
  - National Organization for Women Conference Program, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - NOW's Commission for Responsive Democracy, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - National Peace Action Coalition (Box 19, Folder 22-24)
  - National People's Progressive Network and Convention, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - National Welfare Rights League (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - National Welfare Rights Organization (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - New American Movement (Box 19, Folder 28-31)
  - New Directions Conference Statement, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - New Left (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - New Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - New Politics, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - New Politics Convention, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - New York Intellectuals (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - New York Marxist School (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - New York University - Community Contact Committee (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - News and Letters Committees Constitution and By-laws (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - North Side Youth Action Program (Box 19, Folder 41-42)
  - October 1917 Conference (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Partido Revolucionario de las y los Trabajadores (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Party Struggle (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - The People's Flag (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - People's Liberation Organization and the Provincial Councils Elections, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Peoples' Quincentennial, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - The Philip Murray Institute of Labor Studies, February-March 1990 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Pittsburgh Committee to Defend Political Freedom (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Pittsburgh Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Pittsburgh Peace and Freedom Center (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Progressive Labor Party (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Radical Education Project (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Reserved Officers Training Corp. (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
  - Revolutionary Socialist Union (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Revolutionary Workers League, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rochester Labor Committee (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Ron Daniels for President Campaign, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sierra Club (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Action, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Labor Party (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Workers Party Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Socialist Workers Party 1977 Convention (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Socialist Workers Party 1981 Convention (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Socialist Workers Party Publications (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Solidarity (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Solidarity Constitution, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Solidarity Convention, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Solidarity Correspondence, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Solidarity Draft Discussion Documents, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Solidarity Endorsed Events and Articles, 1991-1993 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Solidarity Forever Calendar, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Solidarity Founding Statement, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Solidarity Member List, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Nicaragua Solidarity Network, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Introduction to Solidarity Packet (Box 20, Folder 29-30)
  - Solidarity Meeting Minutes (Box 20, Folder 31-34)
  - Solidarity Pamphlets (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Other Solidarity Publications (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Polish Solidarity, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Polish Solidarity Controversy, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Solidarity Resolutions, Reports and Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Solidarity Youth Conference, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Surrealist Group (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 21, Folder 6-12)
  - Students for a Democratic Society/Revolutionary Youth Movement (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Student Peace Union (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Temporary Organizing Committee for Marxist-Leninist Youth Organization (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Textile Workers Union of America (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Resistance (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Merton Center (Box 21, Folder 18-19)
  - Thomas Merton Center Board Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Trade Union Commission (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The Trotskyist League (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The Twenty-First Century Party (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - UE (Box 21, Folder 24-26)
  - United Farm Workers of America (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - University of Pittsburgh (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - University of Pittsburgh - National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees, Local 1199p (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Revolutionary Student Union (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - University of Pittsburgh - Young Americans for Freedom (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - U.S. Committee for Justice to Latin America Political Prisoners (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - U.S.-Cuba Friendship IV (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - U.S.-Soviet Worker Information Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - U.S.S.R. Campaign (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Venceremos Brigade (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Vietnam Summer (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Washington Area Peace Action Coalition (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - W.E.B. Club of America (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Women for Racial and Economic Equality, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Women's Liberation (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Workers League (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Workers Power (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Workers Unity Network (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Workers Want Fairness Campaign (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - World Federation of Democratic Youth (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - World Peace Navy (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Young Socialist Alliance (Box 21, Folder 49-50)
  - Young Socialist Alliance Report (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Young Workers Liberation League (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Research, IV.
  This series is composed of both academic and personal research materials collected by LeBlanc. The bulk of the series is composed of readings and articles that usually relate to labor, political or social movements.
  - Miscellaneous Research Material (Box 22-23)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters, Bulletins, Pamphlets and Flyers (Box 24, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper and Magazine Articles (Box 24, Folder 3-7)
  - Miscellaneous Articles and Readings (Box 24, Folder 8-20)
  - Articles from the New International, 1939-1949 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - New York Times Articles (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Article about Canadian Politics (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Articles and Reports about Ernest Mandel, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Articles about Pierre Charles L'Enfant, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 25)